所以，我们首先要做的就是创建一个新的文件。
So the first thing we do is I
will say Create a new file.
在静态资产项目中，我将调用它 Docker 文件。
Here in the static assets project,
I'm gonna call it Docker file.
所以我要在这里说，我们要做一些版本的节点。
So here I'm gonna say FROM and
we're gonna do some version of node.
12 号吧我想我的笔记里有最新的
Let's do 12-stretch,
I think I have latest in my notes, but
你可以为所欲为
you can do it from whatever you want.
让我们从 12 岁开始做我们一直在做的事
Let's do it from 12 stretch,
cuz that's what we've been doing.
给它一个工作目录，让我们称之为 / 应用，或者任何你想说的。
Give it a working directory, let's call
it /app or whatever you wanna call it.
我要和 / 应用
I'm gonna go with /app.
复制所有内容复制点点
Copy everything, copy dot dot,
我们要跑了 NPMCI对吧
and we're gonna do run, NPMCI, right?
要安装我们的依赖关系。
To install of our dependencies.
从技术上来说你可以再在这个下面跑了
And then you could technically
have another run underneath this.
一般情况下，我有多个顺序的东西在运行，对吧 ?
In general when I have multiple
sequential things running, right?
他们都完成了同样的事情，我就做，对吧 ?
And they're all accomplishing relatively
the same thing, I'll just do and, right?
这个还有这个还有这个，对吧 ?
So do this and this and
this and this, right?
这件事对你有多大的帮助，对吧 ?
What's nice about that is that
gets made into one layer, right?
所以它得到了整体的缓存，总体来说，
So it gets cached all together,
which is in general,
你要找的是什么样的行为
what the kind of behavior
you're looking for.
所以我要说恩普，跑，建，对吧 ?
So here I'm going to say nmp,
run, build, right?
库兹我想做最后的项目
Cuz I try like build
out the final project.
所以让我们做个简单的
So let's do this as bulid,
或者类似的东西对吧
or something like that, right?
我们会叫它的建造者来玩
We'll call it builder for fun.
那第二个呢我们就从
So for the second one, we're gonna do FROM
nginx 和我说 1.17是吧
nginx and I said, 1.17, right?
但你完全可以从阿尔派恩来的
But you can totally do this from Alpine,
you can do it from LaTeX,
这对你有多好
that's kind of up to you.
现在我们要做的就是把它从以前的
And now all we need to do is we
need to copy it from the previous
我之前跟你说过的
one into the directory that
I told you before, right?
所以我要说 " COPY"
So I'm gonna say COPY.
我们现在可以创造一个用户和所有这些东西。
And we could create a user and
all that kind of stuff now.
现在让我们忽略一切吧我们都是从根来的
For now let's just ignore,
let's just all do it from root.
所以我要说 FROM =建造者
So I'm gonna say --FROM =builder.
我们会从 /app/build 对吧
And we're gonna do it
from /app/build right?
这就是它能进入的地方对吧
That's where it gets build into, right?
我们会把它复制到 /user/share/nginx/html中。
And we're gonna copy that
into /user/share/nginx/html.
再一次，我告诉过你不要放进一个命令，因为如果你把它放进去，
And again, I told you not to put in
a cmd because if you put in the cmd,
那你就会覆盖些 nginx 的事了
then you're gonna overwrite
what nginx ones is doing.
我们不想这么做我们想让内克斯来处理所有的想法
We don't wanna do that,
we want nginx to handle all the thinks So
就是这样，现在应该是工作了，来试试吧。
that's it, now this should work,
so let's try it.
那我们在哪儿
So where are we?
我们在静态资产项目中。
We are in static-assets-project.
所以我要说码头工人的建筑
So I'm gonna say docker build-t,
let's just
就像静态应用程序之类的
call this like static app or
something like that.
我们应该能够建造，这将会有第二次的反应，要永远做下去。
We should be able to build, this will take
a second cuz react takes forever to build.
我应该说，它是 Web 包， Web 包要永久构建。
I should say, it's web pack,
web pack takes forever to build.
但它会同时运行这两个命令，安装资产。
But it's gonna run both of those commands,
the install the assets.
当它完成后它就会继续
And then as soon as it's done with
that then it's gonna go ahead
并运行我们的建筑
and run our build.
它将输出我们的构建目录。
It's gonna output our build directory.
你知道我在这里做了什么我没意识到
You know what I did in here,
which I didn't realize it,
这还会有效的
this is still gonna work.
你可以在这里看到它现在已经进入了节点 -- 我们走了。
You can see here it's going into
node-sass now, there we go.
现在我们终于进入了建筑过程
Now we're finally into the build process.
但是当它这样做的时候，我从建筑商得到了它的权利。
But while it's doing that,
I got it right from builder.
你也可以从零开始，那是完全可以的。
You can also put from zero here as well,
that would totally work.
这就是我在笔记中所拥有的
And that's what I have in my notes.
好吧那就建了
All right, so that built, And
所以现在要做的是从 nginx 开始下载对吧
so now what's gonna do is,
it's gonna go download from nginx, right?
看来我的电脑上没有它所以它会很快的
Looks like I don't have it on my computer,
so it's gonna go do that really quick.
看起来大概有五十多兆字节
Looks like it's about 50 odd megabytes.
然后把所有东西都复制到那个目录好吗
And then it copied everything from
builder into that directory, okay?
现在我们有了自己的容器。
So now we have our built container.
所以我们要说的是 docker run-P 或者短划线小写 p
So what we're gonna say is, docker run-P,
or dash lower case p rather,
抱歉 8080 您可以在任何要访问的端口上运行此程序。
sorry, 8080, which you can run
this on any port that you want to.
但第一个是主机端口但它会在 80 端口上运行
But the first one's gonna be the host
port, but it is gonna be run on port 80
因为那是 nginx 在默认情况下运行的，对吧 ?
because that's what nginx
runs on by default, right?
我们要从 80 到 80 80 在本地电脑里
So we're gonna go from 80 to 8080
in our local computer, okay?
然后我们要做静态应用
And then we're gonna do static-app.
让我们去看看这是否有用， localhost 8080。
So let's go see if that works,
localhost 8080.
Lo 和 behold，您的应用程序现在正在运行，但这是 nginx 提供的服务，对吗 ?
Lo and behold, your app is now running,
but this is being served by nginx, right?
那么，这又有什么困难呢 ?
So what was hard about that?
你跟什么搏斗了
What did you struggle with?
> > 我们没有忘记需要工作，
&gt;&gt; For us it was not forgetting
that there needs to be working,
以指定工作目录并复制所有文件。
to specify the working directory and
copying all the files.
你懂我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
就像这样一种想法，就像一个空的容器
Like it's kind of like this idea that,
this is basically like an empty container
你得给它带点东西来
you need to bring something in for
it to work with.
> > Mm - m. > 因此
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm.
&gt;&gt; So
有一点断开连接。
there was a little bit of disconnect.
所以其他的都是很清楚的。
So everything else was were very spot on.
只是那个部分
Just that particular part.
因此，当它尝试构建时，我找不到索引文件。
So then as it was trying to build,
I can't find the index file.
我找不到指令
I can't find the directives.
>> 有道理。
&gt;&gt; That makes sense.
嗯。
Yeah.
> > 就好像我什么都没有
&gt;&gt; It's like I don't have anything.
> > ，那肯定是个问题。
&gt;&gt; Yep,
that would definitely be a problem.
希望这一切至少是有道理的如果我们回去再做一次
Hopefully this all at least makes sense,
and if we went back and did it again,
你就能做到了
you would be able to do it.
所以，现在我们只是在使用 nginx 为我们提供的一些缺省配置文件。
So, right now we're just using some
default config file that nginx has for us.
您还可以在 nginx 配置中进行复制，并且
You can also copy in
an nginx configuration, and
然后修改您的 nginx 配置。
then modify your nginx configuration
to however you want to.
它让你也能做到这一点。
It allows you to do that as well.
现在我们不会那么做了，因为我不知道如何配置 nginx 和
Now we're not gonna do that one, because
I don't know how to configure nginx and
我不确定是否有很多人
I'm not sure many people do.
[ LAUGH]. Nginx 很难配置，
[LAUGH].
Nginx is hard to configure,
这就是它的长度和长度
that's the long and the short of it.
[ 笑声 ]
[LAUGH].
所以我们要去做点更多的事情
So we're actually gonna go and
do some more stuff with nginx here in just
第二个，向你们展示我们如何更简单的实现这一点。
a second, to show you how we can
actually even make this even simpler.
我们可以直接运行 nginx 容器而不需要建造它
We can actually run the nginx container
directly without even building it,
也挺有趣的
which is kind of fun as well